Camilla Sundbom

Date of birth: 1984-06-16

Address: Musserongången 192, 135 534 Tyresö

Email: <a href="mailto:camilla.sundbom@me.com">camilla.sundbom@me.com</a>
Phone number: +46 (0)735-08 64 14

### YOUR NEXT EMPLOYEE

Here you have a strong employee who is ready to take on a new challenge.

I am hereby applying for a job with you as I see you as my next challenge.

I choose to see solutions in both my work and personal life, not problems. After my 15 years in service, I think a position with you would suit me perfectly.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Seller 32.5h/v| Office Depot February 2022 - In Progress

I work 6.5h/v at Office Depot, the reason I don't work more than that is because the agreement looks like that, and I've been studying in the meantime.

- Having a good knowledge of the products is important to me as I can confidently support the buyers in their decision.
- Exceptional service to customers.
- Picked up goods and received.
- Cleaned up and rebuilt the store a bit.

#### Studied various courses at Komvux | March 2020 – May 2022

The purpose of these courses was to broaden my knowledge in different areas, such as Swedish, English, mathematics, social studies. I now master programs like C#. Has in-depth knowledge in computer and network technology and has a deeper understanding of English.

Order Administrator/Sales Support 40h/v| SANHA GmbH & Co. KG. KG Filial Sweden April 2019 – March 2020

- Place orders in our own system.
- Send invoices to customers and suppliers.
- Loose picking lists in internal systems.
- Answered questions and resolved situations over the phone.

### Seller 38.25h/v | Office Depot January 2016 – March 2019

- Started in the sales pool in consultation with the then regional manager, where the goal was to help different stores achieve goals and see potential for improvement, had regular meetings with Rc.
- Exceptional service to customers.
- Picked up goods, as well as received.
- Worked together towards budget.
- Worked together towards set goals.
- Ordered Promotions for the coming months.
- Been on total Inventories.

Seller, acting store manager, quality-assurance audio files 38.25h/v| The Phone House 2007-May 2015

- Sold mobiles, subscriptions and accessories to both private and corporate customers.
- -Insurance cases where customers needed help with destroyed mobiles that did not go on the warranty.
- -Inventoried monthly and on an annual basis.
- -Responsible for schedule, time reporting staff, budget, kpi, results during the period that I was tf.bc.
- -Secured audio files between customers and sellers, both corporate and private. Here I have made sure that the sellers' scripts follow the agreements that exist between different retailers.

## **Training**

2020 – 2022 Komvux, Scattered courses.

2017 BAM course handels, main safety representative Office Depot AB.

2000 - 2003 Stockholm Hotel & Restaurant School.

# Other knowledge

Experience from Fakta Pos, M3, MS dos, Office suite is basic, Visual Studio. As well as the CRM system Upsales.

#### Language skills

Swedish: Mother tongue

English: Good knowledge and speech and writing.

B-Driving licence and car

Reference is provided upon request.

Camilla Sundbom